TWUA Executive Council Minutes 6323
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
TWUA Executive Council Minutes
1973-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6323
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Minutes.
7544858
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 11, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Textile Workers Union of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State); Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)
7544858
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: Nov.29-30, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: Oct.14-17, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: June 11-15, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: March 5-8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: Oct.8, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: July 25, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: April 22-25, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: Jan. 27-30, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: May 24-28, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: April 28-30, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: March 16-17, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- TWUA Executive Council Meeting: Jan. 6-9, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)